Woman's Club of Albany; Records mss139
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Woman's Club of Albany Records1908, 1910-2010
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Woman's Club of Albany (Albany, N.Y.)
mss139
23.64 cubic ft. 1
The Woman's Club of Albany Records document the day-to-day operations of the first 100 years of this community organization founded in 1910.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of one folder, which is marked.
Acquisition Information
The Woman's Club of Albany donated all of the materials in this collection to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in April 2012.
Organizational Sketch
Mrs. Elmer Blair, an active member of the New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, and 22 friends who saw an opportunity to make a difference in their community established the Woman's Club of Albany in 1910 based on the motto Let us be such as help the life of the future. The Womans Club of Albany dedicated itself to helping women and children as well as improving conditions in its surrounding area.
Membership within the Womans Club of Albany (WCA) grew quickly, reaching three hundred members by the end of its second year. In 1913 the WCA was incorporated and in 1919, it purchased its Clubhouse, located at 725 Madison Avenue. The members were divided into multiple departments, sections, and committees, focusing on various goals and issues. Within the first ten years of its existence, the WCA discussed timely issues such as Medical inspection of the Public Schools, began programs to help children stay off the streets, and even campaigned to have a woman member added to the City's Board of Education. By the 1930s and the beginning of the 1940s the WCA flourished; sufficient funds, an array of events and programs, and a membership of six hundred women, including honorary members. Honorary members were often the current New York State Governors wife, such as future President Franklin Delano Roosevelts wife, Eleanor Roosevelt. During this time period, the WCA also raised awareness of international conflict and often contributed to war efforts.
During the second half of the twentieth century, the WCA attempted to reinvent itself as membership dropped, the number of departments decreased, and the Clubs financial situation began a decline. In the 1970s the WCA tried to overhaul its image by shifting from activities with a civic emphasis to more social ones. By the 1980s the WCA once again tried to revitalize the organization by establishing itself as a center of cooperation among women in New York's Capital District for civic, literary, and philanthropic works.
Despite these attempts, the WCA continued to decline into the beginning years of the twenty first century. By the end of 2003 only three elderly members remained, the Clubhouse needed repairs, and the future of the WCA was in jeopardy. In 2004 five new women discovered the WCA while attending an event hosted in the rented Clubhouse. They joined the organization and were determined to revive it as a center of activity once again benefiting the surrounding community. Since 2004, the Womans Club of Albany has witnessed great improvement; membership is consistently increasing among women of all ages, the organization has undertaken restoration projects in the Clubhouse, and the WCA is once again involving itself in various philanthropic activities within the City of Albany and the surrounding Capital District.
Scope and Contents
The Womans Club of Albany Records include one hundred years' worth of information about all aspects of the Club. The collection is divided into eight series according to the organizational structure and activities of the WCA, flowing from the Board of Directors down to the members. It contains meeting minutes and annual reports for not only the Board of Directors, but for many of the different departments and committees. This will give researchers insight into what members discussed, the goals and focuses of groups within the WCA, and how all of these evolved throughout the years. The WCAs financial history is organized chronologically from the WCAs beginning in 1910 to its revitalization in recent years. This series contains a range of materials, from financial statements to general receipts to loan and mortgage paperwork. Most folders are ordered according to department or committee. As the financial papers were often kept in separate envelopes denoting a particular year and group within the WCA, the archivist retained this original order.
This collection also documents the membership of the WCA. Researchers should note that the Membership series is broken down into five separate subseries. There are both paper records and three sets of index cards; one set is comprised of early membership cards, another is a set of cards documenting individual resignations and dropped members ranging from the 1920s to the 1970s, and the last set is of cards recording the deaths of members. The use of multiple subseries reflects the original order of the content and preserves WCA's record keeping, which often changed over time.
Events and programs hosted by the WCA comprise their own series. The WCA hosted a range of events, such as rummage sales, plays, and an annual WCA anniversary dinner. Another series documents items published by the WCA. This includes event calendars sent to the members and copies of The Messenger, the WCAs monthly events publication. A subject file series contains information on a variety of topics, from materials about the New York Federation of Women's Clubs to WCA histories to an engineering/structural report on the Clubhouse.
Please note that the scrapbook series provides a significant amount of information about not only the WCA itself, but also the ever-changing world around it. Part of the series is unavailable to researchers and being evaluated for possible preservation treatment because of the delicate and fragile conditions of some of the scrapbooks.
It should be noted that the amount of content often coincides with the ebb and flow of the WCA's history. There is a generous amount of information available from the early decades when the WCA was prosperous, as well from the revitalization of the WCA in 2004 and beyond. There is much material missing from the late 1960s through the 1990s, which is when the WCA was not robust in terms of members or finances. This historical evolution is seen in The Messenger. The Messenger began as a glossy magazine in the 1940s, but the WCA continually shortened the publication, transitioning first to a newsletter on legal sized paper and then to a newsletter on letter sized paper by the early 1970s.
Arrangement of the Collection
All series are arranged chronologically with the exception of Series 4, Subseries 1, 2, 4, and 5, which are arranged alphabetically.
Women; Neighborhood and Community Associations; Women--New York (State)--Albany--Societies and clubs; Women in nonprofit organizations--New York (State)--Albany; Amateur plays; Fundraising--New York (State)--Albany; Women in charitable work--New York (State)--Albany; New York (State)--Social conditions; Scrapbooks; Newsletters; Administrative records; Membership cards; Minutes; Programs (documents); Financial Records; Photographs; Digital Files; The Woman's Club of Albany (Albany, N.Y.); New York State Federation of Womens Clubs
- Administrative, 1910-2010; 1; 1.88 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The Administrative series consists of Board and business meeting minutes, constitutions, proposed changes to the constitution, annual and executive meeting files, files of some Club Presidents, and rules and regulations.
  Please note that the Board and business meeting minutes are kept together to preserve original order. This series also contains multiple versions of the Womans Club of Albany Constitution: ca. 1910, 1946, and 1981. It also includes proposed changes to the Constitution from 1912, 2006 and an unknown year.
  - Minutes of the Board of Directors, 1910-1920 (Oversized 1)
  - Minutes of the Business Meetings and the Annual Reports, 1910-1920 (Oversized 1)
  - Constitution, ca. 1910 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting, 1911 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - Proposed Changes to Constitution to Members from Board, 1912 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - Incorporation Papers and Correspondence, 1912-1913; 1915; 1917 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1913 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting Address of the President, 1914 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Resolution to Adapt National Constitution Prohibition, 1916 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting Address of the President, 1916 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Board and Business Meeting Reports, 1920-1922 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes, 1924-1926 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - Letters from the Board to Department Leaders and Members, 1924-1938; 1945; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes, 1926-1928 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting, 1927 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 12)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes, 1930-1932 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 13)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes, 1932-1934 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 14)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1934-1938 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 15)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1934-1938 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 16)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1938-1943 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 17)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1938-1943 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 18)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1944-1946 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 19)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1944-1946 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 20)
  - Club Constitution, 1946 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 21)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1946-1952 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 22)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1946-1952 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 23)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1952-1958 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 24)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1952-1958 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 25)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1952-1958 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 26)
  - Executive Report, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 27)
  - Annual Meeting, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 28)
  - Executive Reports and Annual Meetings, 1959 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 29)
  - Executive Reports and Annual Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 30)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 31)
  - Executive Reports and Annual Meetings, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 32)
  - Executive Reports and Annual Meetings, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 33)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 34)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 35)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes w/ Treasurer Reports, 1964-1968 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 36)
  - Presidential File, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 37)
  - File of the Corresponding Secretary (1 of 2), 1968-1971 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 38)
  - File of the Corresponding Secretary (2 of 2), 1968-1971 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 39)
  - File of the Corresponding Secretary, 1971-1976 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - Board and Business Meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1976-1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1976-1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1976-1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - Constitution, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Letters about Proposed Changes to Constitution sent to Members from Board, 1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1982-1986 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1982-1986 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - Presidential File, Stella Porter, 1987-1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - Message to the Club from the Board, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 12)
  - Presidential File, Eunice Hunter (1 of 2), 1996-2004; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 13)
  - Presidential File, Eunice Hunter (2 of 2), 1996-2004; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 14)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - Meeting Agenda, 2006 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - Proposed Changes to the Constitution, 2006 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - Organization Bylaws of the Club, 2008 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Board Roster, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Board and Business Meeting Minutes, 2009 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - Certificate of Incorporation and Related Papers, 2009 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Board Roster, 2009-2010 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - President's Message, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - Proposed Changes to Constitution, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - Proposed Changes to Constitution, Bylaws, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - Resolutions Passed by Administration Based on Deceased Members, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 12)
  - Responsibilities of Corresponding Secretary by Month, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 13)
  - Rules and Regulations, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 14)
- Financials, 1910-2009; 2; 7.17 cubic ft.
  Series two contains one hundred years' worth of financial information pertaining to the WCA. A majority of the series consists of various departments and committees expenses, receipts, and annual reports. These were originally kept in envelopes according to department or committee and year. There are also Office and Treasurer Reports spanning from 1912 to 2009, providing information about the WCAs treasury and daily spending. Please note that there are no reports from the early 1930s, 1940s or late 1950s. Financial statements provide an inside look into the WCAs evolutionary financial health.
  The series also contains insurance policies and payments from 1919 to 2005. The WCA retained all mortgage and loan agreements, and payment information, allowing researchers to see when the WCA purchased its house and exactly how long it took to pay off the house and loan. The WCA donated multiple ledgers and accounting books, which are stored separately in oversized, flat boxes.
  - Journal and Cash Book, 1910-1920 (Oversized 3)
  - Bank Passbooks, 1910-1993 (Card-file 5)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1910 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1911 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - Literature Department Expenses, 1911 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - NYS Federation of Women's Club Convention and Membership Dues, 1911-1974 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - House Committee Expenses, 1911-1914; 1918 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - Costumes Committee Expenses, 1912 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1912 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Printing Committee Expenses, 1912 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - Public Education Expenses, 1912 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Social and Industrial Department Receipts, 1912 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - Home Economics Department Expenses, 1912-1914 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - Financial Correspondence and Expenses of the Dramatic Department and Language Department, 1912-1914 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Hotel Hampton Bills and Various Receipts, 1912-1914 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Financial Correspondence (1 of 4), 1912-1996 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - Financial Correspondence (2 of 4), 1912-1996 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - Financial Correspondence (3 of 4), 1912-1996 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - Financial Correspondence (4 of 4), 1912-1996 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - Office and Treasurer Reports (1 of 6), 1912-2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Office and Treasurer Reports (2 of 6), 1912-2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - Office and Treasurer Reports (3 of 6), 1912-2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Office and Treasurer Reports (4 of 6), 1912-2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - Office and Treasurer Reports (5 of 6), 1912-2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - Office and Treasurer Reports (6 of 6), 1912-2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - Parliamentary Law Expenses and Rentals, 1912; 1914-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1913 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - Handwritten Financial Statements, 1913-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - Municipal Welfare Department, and Social and Industrial Department Expenses, 1913-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Music Department Expenses, 1913-1915; 1917-1918 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - Notice of Membership Dues, 1913; 1924; 1934; Undated (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1914 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - Civic Section, Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1914-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - Language Department Expenses, 1914-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - Office and Unclassified Expenses, 1914-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - French Department Expenses, 1914-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1914-1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - Fine Arts Department Expenses, 1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 37)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1915 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 38)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1915-1916 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 39)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1915-1929 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 40)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1916 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 41)
  - Literature Department Expenses, 1916 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 42)
  - Supervised Dances, Gifts, Contributions, and Relief Committee Expenses, 1916 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 43)
  - Printing, Stationary, and Yearbook Receipts, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 44)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 45)
  - Fine Arts Department Expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 46)
  - Gift Contributions and Supervised Dances Expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 47)
  - Language Department Expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 48)
  - Housing Committee and Literature Department Receipts, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 49)
  - Domestic Arts and Sciences Department Expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 50)
  - Social Committee Receipts, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 51)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 1 (2-Financials), Folder 52)
  - Department of Registrations Expenses, 1917 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements, 1917; Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - Fine Arts Department Expenses, 1917 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1917 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Peace and Patriotism Committee Expenses, 1917 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1917 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - Culinary Science Section and House Arts and Crafts Section Expenses, 1917-1918 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - Yearbook Committee Expenses, 1917; 1919-1920 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Bank Statements, 1917-1920; ca. 1910s (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - Handwritten Financial Statements, 1917-1926; Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
  - Audit Information, 1917; 1923-1927; 1930; 1977 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1918 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - Art Department Expenses, 1918-1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - Office Expenses, 1918-1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Parliamentary Law Expenses and Misc. Receipts, 1918-1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Supervised Dance Expenses and Various Receipts, 1918-1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - Legal Matters of Deceased Members' Estates - [RESTRICTED], 1918; 1953; 1977-1979 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - Housing Committee and Literature Department Expenses, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Arts and Crafts Section Expenses, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - Loan Papers, 1919-1922; 1930 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Literature Department Expenses, 1919-1920 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - Mortgage Paperwork and Payments, 1919-1921; 1925-1938 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - City of Albany Taxes (1 of 2), 1919-1999 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - City of Albany Taxes (2 of 2), 1919-1999 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - Membership Committee Expenses, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1920 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Fine Arts Department Expenses, 1920-1921 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - Office Expenses and Language Department Expenses, 1920-1921 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1920-1921; 1923 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1921 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - Bank Statements, 1921-1922 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - Music Section Expenses, 1921-1922 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1921-1922 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - Receipts and Annual Reports of Various Committees, 1921-1927 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1922 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Courtesy Committee and Emergency Committee Expenses, 1922-1923 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 37)
  - Fine Art Department Expenses, 1922-1923 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 38)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1922-1923 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 39)
  - Entertainment Committee Expenses, 1923 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 40)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1923 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 41)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Expenses, 1923-1924 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 42)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1923-1924 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 43)
  - Unbound Accounting Ledger Pages, 1923-1924 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 44)
  - Bank Statements, 1923-1925 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 45)
  - Music Department Expenses, 1923; 1927; 1929 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 46)
  - Fine Arts Department Expenses, 1924 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 47)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1924 (Box 2 (2-Financials), Folder 48)